准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
死亡馅饼
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
上菜了  章鱼哥
Order up, Squidward
蟹堡王
别问我今天过得怎样
章鱼哥  你刚看到我了没
Squidward, did you see me?
那就等会见  章鱼同事
Okay, see you later, Squidinater
此处点餐
早安  章鱼哥先生
Good morning, Mr. Squidward
那么  你准备好了吗
So, are you ready?
准备好回家吗
To go home?
错  是准备好为员工情谊日交换礼物
No, to exchange gifts for employee brotherhood day
蟹老板  虽然你可以付工钱雇我收银
Mr. Krabs, you pay me to stand behind this register
然后接单然后找零钱
and take orders and give change
但就算你给的工钱再多
but you could never pay me enough
都不可能让我情深意重对待
to act brotherly toward
那个家伙
that guy
正因为你这种态度
That attitude of yours
才要使出这种小把戏
is precisely why we're having this little shenanigan
注意好了
Now, pay attention
那小子有个惊喜要送你
The lad's got a surprise for you
章鱼哥  为了敬重我们的员工情谊
Squidward, in honor of employee brotherhood
我要送你一份礼物
I present to you a gift
哒哒
Ta-dah
我爱你
"I heart you"
试穿下吧  章鱼哥先生
Try it on, Mr. Squidward
上面画满了你的脸  一看就是给你的
It's got you written all over it
我不太确定要留多大的洞塞头
I wasn't sure how big to make the hole for the head
所以我就用西瓜来试尺寸
so I used a watermelon for size
你喜欢吗
Do you love it?
有点痒
It's a little itchy
这用什么做的
What's this thing made of?
眼睫毛
Eyelashes
现在我可以继续干活拿最低工资了吗
Now, may I resume my minimum-wage duties?
先送出你的情谊礼物再说
After you present your brotherhood gift
我会给那白痴买颗口香糖
I'll buy the little twerp a gumball
不行不行不行  小子
Oh, no, no, no, lad
你可是知道规矩的
you know the rules
礼物必须自己做
you have to make the gift
我唯一想要做的就是出门
The only thing I'm making is for the exit
这样好点了没  章鱼哥
Is this any better, Squidward?
我用泪水做的这件毛衣
I made this one with my tears
就知道你会改变主意  小子
I knew you'd come around, boy
做个好礼物出来
Make something nice
干嘛不能给那小怪胎随便买样礼物
Why can't I just buy something for the little weirdo?
使劲
Heave ho
要是把我财宝搞掉下来一块
If you drop one single slice of me booty
我就要
I'll have
割你们屁股
your booty
你们好
Hi, there
那些家常手工派看起来挺好吃的
Those homemade pies sure look good
不是家常手工的
These aren't homemade
是工厂制造的
They were made in a factory
炸弹工厂
a bomb factory
这些是炸弹
They're bombs
好可惜
Well, that's too bad
我还以为那些是派  本来还想买的
I thought they were pies and I wanted to buy one
且慢
Wait
我们刚刚说的炸弹都是玩笑话
We were just kidding about all that bomb stuff
付二十五块钱就能买了
That'll be 25 bucks, please
所以说这什么味的
So, what flavor is it?
樱桃
Cherry
苹果
Apple
山莓
Raspberry
能让那个蟹老头别烦我就行了
Well, if it gets old man Krabs off my back
礼物做好了  蟹老板
Okay, here it is, Mr. Krabs
新鲜出炉
fresh from the oven
现在我要回归正常生活了
I'll be returning to my life now
还不行
Not yet
我得确定下你礼物做得行不行
I got to make sure you did it right
等一下
Wait a second
配牛奶更好吃
This would go great with some milk
牛奶
原来你想杀了我
So, you tried to kill me
好改旗易帜是吧
over a little New-Age management, eh?
可是蟹老板  我不知道会这样
But Mr. Krabs, I had no idea
我能解释清楚
I can explain
蟹老板  没事吧
Mr. Krabs, are you okay?
我听到有
I heard a
有派
A pie
是章鱼哥送的
It's from Squidward
海绵宝宝收
"To SpongeBob
章鱼哥送
海绵宝宝收
你爱拿就拿吧
Well, here you go"
经过就是这样
And that's what happened
二十五块钱
25 dollars?
炸弹
A bomb?
还在蟹堡王里
In the Krusty Krab?
你刚把它放这了的
That's where you left it
不见了
It's not there
各位
Hey, guys
谢谢你送的派  章鱼哥
Thanks for the pie, Squidward
你还非得杀了他不可
You had to kill him
那小子用泪水给你哭出了件毛衣
The boy cries you a sweater of tears
你却要杀了他
and you kill him
怎么有脸心安理得活下去的
How are you going to live with yourself?
杀了他
Kill him?
你的餐来了  先生
Here's your order, sir
谢了
Thanks
不行  要怎么
no, no, what we got
得给医院打电话
we got to call the hospital
没救了
Won't do any good
我先前就见过这种情况
I've seen this before
等到那派登上了本垒板
When that pie goes up to bat
我是说  等到抵达他下肠道
I mean, hit his lower intestine
你先前就见过了
You've seen this before?
其实见了有十一次
11 times, as a matter of fact
喂  医生吗
Yes, hello, doctor?
医院吗
Hospital?
都没救了
It won't do any good?
十一次
Eleven times?
他死定了
He's a goner
得怎样交代人家
How do we tell him?
不要交代
Don't tell him
说了只会让人家更难受
that'll only make him feel worse
依我看  他只能活到日落时分
The way I see it, he's only got till sunset
为何要毁掉他活在世上的最后一天
Why ruin his last day on earth?
那小子理应享受他最后的光阴
The lad deserves to enjoy his final hours
说得对  蟹老板
You're right, Mr. Krabs
我要让海绵宝宝最后的光阴
l'm going to make SpongeBob's final hours
成为他最美好的光阴
the best he's ever had
这回  我要投入爱
And this time, there's going to be love
多到能淹死他
so much he's going to drown in it
淹死他
Drown in it
写给自己  小心章鱼哥
"Note to self: Watch out for Squidward"
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
怎么了
Yes?
我忘了跟你说
I forgot to tell you
你礼物还有第二部分
there's a part two to your gift
第二部分吗
"Part two"?
第二部分
Part two
别给我这样干
Please don't do that
第二部分要干嘛
What's for part two?
你能想到什么最快乐的事呢
Well, what's the most fun thing you can think of?
其实我记了张清单
Actually, I keep a list
里面列了我所有爱做的快乐事情
of the most fun things I like to do
我管这单子叫  情谊单
I call it my "friendship list"
好棒
Great
让我瞧一瞧
Let me see it
更快乐的事情
The things that are extra fun
都标成红色了
I've written in red
全都是红色的
Everything's in red
对啊  我知道
Yeah, I know
想完事最好现在就开始干
We'd better start now if want to get through this list
免得你死
before you die
思来想去
of anticipation
那就开整吧
Then let's roll
再见  蟹老板
Bye, Mr. Krabs
招聘
看下  章鱼哥
Heads up, Squidward
你好像要被换掉了
looks like they're going to replace you
还行吧
Yeah
来看下单子
Now let's have a look at that list
我想做的第一件事
Well, the first thing I want to do
是把我最好的朋友章鱼哥
is show my best friend, Squidward
介绍给全镇人
to everybody in town
你好  这是我最好的朋友章鱼哥
Hi there, this is my best friend, Squidward
小朋友们  快来看
Hey, kids, check it out
这是我最好的朋友章鱼哥
This is my best friend, Squidward
嗨  我想向你介绍
Hi, I want to show you
我最好的朋友章鱼哥
my best friend, Squidward
法兰克
Hey, Frank
真高兴介绍完了
Glad that's over
很好  因为我们要干下一件事了
Good, 'cause we're on to our next activity
这件事是
Which is?
我要把我最好的朋友章鱼哥
I'm going to show my best friend, Squidward
介绍给全镇人  但要先穿上鲑鱼装
to everyone in town wearing a salmon suit
你居然要穿鲑鱼装
You're going to be wearing a salmon suit?
真好笑  章鱼哥
That's a good one, Squidward
介绍穿鲑鱼装的
下一件
Next
敲门笑话
Knock-knock jokes
章鱼哥  有人敲门
Hey, Squid, knock-knock
谁啊
Who's there?
我啊
I am
真好啊
Oh, yeah
敲门笑话
请注意  倒朋友
Look out, everyone, friends in reverse
假装倒车
模仿猿猴
左转  再
Turn left, and
停
stop
这下明白拿我当脸用会怎样了吧
See, that's what it would be like if you had me for a face
我喘不过气了
I can't breathe
交换脸
你确定应该要这样子戳吗
Are you sure you should be poking it like that?
也不看看这边谁是医生
Who's the doctor here?
剖心
杂耍
介绍穿鲑鱼装的
单子上的最后一件事是
the last thing on the list is
是不是还有肢解
does it involve more dismemberment?
跟章鱼哥一起看日落
"Watch the sunset with Squidward"
日落
"Sunset"?
依我看  那小子只能活到日落时分
The way I see it, the lad's got until sunset
届时那炸弹会命中他的下肠道
before that bomb hits his lower intestine
是蟹老板
It's Mr. Krabs
嗨  蟹老板
Hi, Mr. Krabs
那好  再见了
Okay, see you later
来吧  兄弟
Come on, buddy
你要日落  那就给你日落
you want a sunset, you'll get a sunset
水下日落
Underwater sunsets
真美啊  对吧章鱼哥
sure are beautiful eh, Squidward?
对
Yeah
是啊
只有我们三个可真棒啊
Yeah, this is great just the three of us
你  我
you, me
还有你在我们中间修的这堵砖墙
and this brick wall you built between us
是啊
Yeah
我看日落会想到碗装的水果
sunsets remind me of bowls of fruit
你看日落会想到什么  章鱼哥
What do they make you think of, Squidward?
爆炸
explosions
我是说  贬值
I mean, erosion
假如我现在就会被炸死
You know, if I were to die right now
in some sort of fiery explosion
起因都是有位朋友粗心大意
due to the carelessness of a friend
那也倒没事
well, that would just be okay
感觉好像有东西
If feels like something
掉到我下肠道了
just dropped into my lower intestine
闻着好像樱桃
Smells like cherry
或许是葡萄
Or maybe grape
还是蓝莓
Blueberry?
日落  终于到了
Here it is, the sunset
我特别喜欢这时候倒计时
I always love to count it down
五
Five
你数剩下的  兄弟
You do the rest, buddy
四
Four
三
three
二
t-two
一
one
好像数得太早了
I guess we started too early
重新数一遍吧
Let's start again
五  四
Five, four
三
three
二
two
一
One
好吧  至少我还能
Well, at least I was able
让他最后的光阴有了意义
to make his last few hours meaningful
我可真是大好人
I am such a good person
章鱼哥  瞧瞧这招
Hey, Squidward, check this out
章鱼哥  都已经学过傻子胡言乱语了
Squidward, we already played "Babble Like an Idiot"
你怎么还好端端在这
Why are you still here?
单子上的事情都做完了
Since we finished everything on the list
所以我就想再列一份
I thought I'd made up a new one
这本书的创意都已经想好了
I already filled up this book with ideas
永远好朋友
到一月份应该就能写完了
We should be able to finish by January
书先别管
Forget the book
之所以我花上一整天陪你一起
I spent the whole day with you
做各种荒唐可笑的事情
doing all kinds of ridiculous things
是因为你本来应该要爆了才对
because you were supposed to explode
你要我暴
You want me to explode?
对
Yes
我就一直在等你爆了
That's what I've been waiting for
那好吧  我尽力
Okay, I'll try
小蜗
Gary
你要吃完甜点
You are going to finish your dessert
保证你会爱上的
and you are going to like it
现在轮你了
Now, it's your turn
我想说的不是暴怒的暴  你个呆头
That's not what I meant, you barnacle head
暴得不错
Good one
个鬼  你应该爆炸成几百万块才对
No, you're supposed to explode into a million pieces
为什么应该要那样
Why would I do that?
因为你吃的那个派是炸弹
Because the pie you ate was a bomb
什么派
What pie?
今天一大早我放柜台上的
The one I left sitting on the counter this morning
还找海盗付了二十五块买的
that I bought from pirates for 25 bucks
我都不知道是炸弹的
and I didn't know was a bomb
还被你吃掉了的  那个派
and you ate it, that pie
派
Pie?
你是说这个派啊
You mean this pie
我一直放口袋里要跟你一起分着吃
I was saving it in my pocket for us to share
来吃吧
Let's eat
裤头村
真假蟹老板
导演
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
啊  蟹堡王
Ah, the Krusty Krab
蟹堡王
蟹黄堡之家  内有十分机密的秘方
home of the Krabby Patty, with its top secret formula
只有足够勇敢足够聪明的人
known only to those brave enough
and intelligent enough
才能领略其中的奥妙
to comprehend its culinary complexity
蟹老板快看
Look, Mr. Krabs
我做到了  我做到了
I'm doing it, l'm doing it
别卖傻了  海绵宝宝
Quit fooling around, SpongeBob
还有客人在等
we've got customers
蟹堡王
但凡哪里有份秘方
But wherever there is a secret recipe
总会有人想要去偷
there is someone who wants to steal it
现在再来最后一步
And now for the final touch
完美
Perfect
伪装在手  秘方我有
With this disguise that formula is as good as mine
你是海绵宝宝吗
Are you SpongeBob SquarePants?
是啊
Why, yes
在下正是
yes, I am
那你刚刚赢得了一百万块钱
Then you've just won $1 million
只要回答我一个问题
You just have to answer one question
蟹黄堡的秘密配方是什么
What is the Krabby Patty secret formula?
是什么
Yes
蟹黄堡的秘密配方
The Krabby patty formula
为蟹堡王之私有财产
is the sole property of the Krusty Krab
部分或整体仅能与发明者蟹老板讨论
and is only to be discussed, in part or in whole
with its creator Mr. Krabs
擅自复制秘方将会受法律处罚
Duplication of this formula is punishable by law
处罚力度视程度而定
Restrictions apply, results may vary
够了
That's it
给我把秘方说出来  不然有你好受的
You'd better cough up that secret formula or else
痞老板
Plankton
蟹老板
Krabs
痞老板
Plankton
蟹老板
Krabs
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你不可以对我这样做  老螃蟹
You can't do this to me, Krabs
我上过大学的
I went to college
海之霸
痞老板那畜生可精明了
That Plankton is a clever beast
你最好要密切注意好他  海绵宝宝
You've got to keep a sharp eye out for him, SpongeBob
蟹黄堡法必须要严格实行
The Krabby Patty law must be enforced
蟹堡王的未来全都靠在那上面了
The future of the Krusty Krab depends on it
你放心  蟹老板
Don't worry, Mr. Krabs
只要我这裤子还是方的
As long as these pants are square
我这海绵还是宝宝的
and this sponge is bob
放 你 下 来
我绝对不会让你失望的
I will not let you down
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
能放我下来吗
could you let me down?
蟹堡王
老天啊  这些蟹黄堡可真是好吃
Man, these patties sure are delicious
不知道这秘方里面加了什么
I wonder what's in that secret formula?
十二号警报
Code 12
你这回的伪装可骗不到我  痞老板
Your disguises can't fool me this time, Plankton
头部增强诊所的所有人
Everyone at the Head Enhancement Clinic
明明说过没人会注意的
said nobody would notice
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你把我钱给吓跑了
You're scaring away me money
抱歉  蟹老板
Sorry, Mr. Krabs
我只是尽了力在保护秘密配方
I'm just trying to protect the secret formula
就算那样也不能乱扒别人脑袋  小子
That's no reason to rip people's heads off, boy
只要记好最重要的规矩
Just remember the most important rule
不提供免费纸巾
No free napkins?
错
No
另外一条最重要的规矩
The other most important rule
讲秘方的那条
regarding the secret formula
只能跟蟹老板讨论秘方
Only discuss the secret recipe with Mr. Krabs
只要你这办妥了  秘方就安全了
As long as you do that, the secret is safe
我还一直以为最重要的规矩就是
l always thought the most important rule was
能拖到明天  干嘛今天做
"Why do today what you can put off till tomorrow?"
今天个鬼  不是昨天的明天吗
What is today but yesterday's tomorrow?
今天我要让你清查这边的所有东西
Today, I want you to take inventory
on everything in here
每块腌椰菜每块肉饼都得记下来
every last pickle and patty must be accounted for
遵命船长
Aye, aye, captain
两箱面包
Two boxes of buns
三磅肉饼
Three pounds of patties
章鱼哥先生
Mr. Squidward
又怎么了  蟹老板
What now, Mr. Krabs?
没错  我就是蟹老板
That's right, I am Krabs
你的老板  你的统治者
your boss, your ruler
你的主人
your master
你可不是蟹老板
You're not Mr. Krabs
要不让你今天剩下时间休假吧
Why don't you take the rest of the day off?
那个啊
Well
那就听你的了  蟹老板
whatever you say, "Mr. Krabs"
嗨  蟹老板
Hi, Mr. Krabs
控制易如反掌
Sweet domination
这就对了
This is it
还没有痞老板的踪迹
No sign of Plankton yet
老天爷啊  蟹老板
Gosh, Mr. Krabs
你好像不舒服
you don't look so good
你好冷
You're so cold
那只是我的铁布衫
That's just my metal suit
用来保护秘方的
I made it to protect the formula
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
是呆头老螃蟹
It's that thick-headed Krabs
他会坏了我的好事的
He'll ruin everything
快看  有只水母
Look, a jellyfish
我来捉  我来捉
I got it, I got it
中止
我来捉  我来捉
I got it, I got it
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
蟹老板  你铁布裤怎么了
Hey, Mr. Krabs, what happened to your metal pants?
别给我弄什么怪异行为  小子
Don't go all loopy on me, boy
我要你来帮忙
I need your help
章鱼哥到底跑哪去了
And where in the high seas is Squidward?
你让他休假了
You gave him the day off
休
Day
假
Off
我都不知道这俩奇葩的字是几个意思
I don't know the meaning of them horrible words
别给我躺平了  海绵宝宝
Now quit your laying around, SpongeBob
垃圾都拿出去倒掉
and take out that garbage
都快害我起疹子了
It's starting to give me a rash
遵命  蟹老板大人
Yes, sir, Mr. Krabs, sir
蟹老板  只是要出去倒垃圾而已
Hey, Mr. Krabs, just taking out that garbage
不用管垃圾了
Never mind that
我需要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
我都不知道你还长了放热电光眼
l didn't know you had heat vision
你管不着  我需要你告诉我
Never mind, I need you to tell me
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
我付你工钱不是来雇你偷懒的
I'm not paying you to stand around
快回厨房里去
Get back to the kitchen
可我还以为你要问我问题
But I thought you wanted to ask me a question
确实要问
Yes
你怎么不再努力点工作
why aren't you working harder?
我搞不懂  蟹老板
I don't know, Mr. Krabs
我搞不懂
I don't know
蟹老板老是进进出出的
I'll never get that formula with that pest, Krabs
我肯定就拿不到秘方
popping in and out like that
有了
I've got it
我一直就存着这玩意以防万一
I've been saving this for a rainy day
看起来像是普普通通的一分钱
lt looks like an ordinary penny
因为本来就是普普通通的一分钱
because it is an ordinary penny
那笨蛋老螃蟹可贪了
That fool Krabs is too greedy
绝对不会忽略你  我的小可爱
to ignore you, my little pretty
这声音  听着像
That sound, it sounds like
叮当作响的
the pitter-patter of
钱
money
你要跑哪去  美人
Where you going, beautiful?
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
别跑了
Stop
求你了
Please
等等我
Wait
我跟秘方之间没有障碍了
Nothing stands between me and that secret formula now
擦擦擦  我喜欢擦
Scrubba-dub-dub, l love to rub
蟹老板  擦个地板而已
Hey, Mr. Krabs, just doing a little scrubbing
你好  海绵宝宝
Hello, SpongeBob
是我  蟹老板
it is me, Mr. Krabs
本人
in the flesh
就站在你面前
standing right in front of you
旁边没一个外人
with no one else around
这我知道  蟹老板
I can see that, Mr. Krabs
我觉得应该可以讨论蟹黄堡秘方了
I thought we might discuss
the Krabby Patty secret formula
这不一话筒吗
Isn't that a microphone?
什么
What?
还确实是
Why, yes, it is
我必须得把这铁布衫给洗洗了
I must get this shirt cleaned
好了  现在给我说秘方
All right, now tell me the secret formula
可是老板  还没做秘密握手式
But, sir, we haven't done the secret handshake yet
确实  来握手吧
Oh, yes, here, let's shake
握手式不握手  忘了吗
We don't shake with our hands, remember?
对  那你先来吧
Right, why don't you start
单脚独立
We stand on one foot
拿杯巧克力奶稳稳顶在头上
balance a glass of chocolate milk on our heads
唱裤头村村歌
and sing the Bikini Bottom national anthem
哦  裤头村
Oh, Bikini Bottom
我们对你起誓
We pledge our hearts to you
共忠实  共深沉
As faithful, as deep
共真诚  共蔚蓝
as true, as blue
裤头村我们爱你
Bikini Bottom, we love you
该说秘方了吧
Formula time?
快了
Almost
六个半小时后
好吃  这意大利面真不错
Yum, yum, this spaghetti sure is good
打嗝
Belch
肉丸肉丸  下面放着意大利面
Meatball, meatball, spaghetti underneath
方饺方饺  简直如同大堡礁
Ravioli, ravioli, Great Barrier Reef
好了  讲点秘方的事吧
Okay, now let's hear that formula
抱歉
Sorry
还不行  蟹老板
no can do, Mr. Krabs
什么
Wha-a-a-a-t?
可你说的都照办了
But we did everything you said
所有规矩我都遵守了
I followed all the rules
我还都用吸管吃了105颗甘草糖豆
I even ate 105 black licorice jelly beans
through a straw
凭什么不能告诉我秘方
Now, why can't you tell me the formula?
是你定的规矩啊
It's your rule
不能把秘方给说出来
never speak the formula
你交代过我要把秘方装进
You told me to keep it in
这个瓶子里
this bottle
这就对了  痞老板
This is it, Plankton
轻一点
Gently, now
倒抽一口气
Gasp
你怎么能这样  海绵宝宝
How could you do this, SpongeBob?
把我的秘方交给这个
Giving me secret formula to this
冒牌货
impostor?
不要听他话  海绵宝宝
Don't listen to him, SpongeBob
别忘了
Remember
方饺方饺  快给我送秘方来
ravioli, ravioli, give me the formuoli
海绵宝宝  别
SpongeBob, no
别听他的话
don't listen to him
我才是真正的蟹老板
I'm the real Mr. Krabs
不要听他的话  他明显是个机器人
Don't listen to him, he's obviously a robot
我要是个机器人  虽然本来就不是
Well, if I was a robot, which I'm not
至少我组装得特像模像样
at least I'm well put together
不像是某些蒸汽发动的生锈废铁
not some rusted-out, steam-driven pile of junk
你说谁是蒸汽发动的
Who you calling "steam-driven"?
肃静
Quiet
等我知道谁才是真蟹老板才可以动
Until I know who the real Mr. Krabs is, nobody moves
塔塔酱
在此之前没人会受伤
nobody gets hurt
塔塔酱
Tartar sauce?
悠着点使那玩意  小子
Take it easy with that thing, son
我才有话语权
I'll do the talking around here
我要向你们两个问一点问题
I think I'll just ask you two a couple of questions
只有真正的蟹老板才答得上来的问题
questions only the real Mr. Krabs could answer
那就好
Okay, then
第一题  蟹堡王几点几分开门
First question: What time does the Krusty Krab open?
上午九点半
9:30 a.m.
答对了
Right
第一招就中了  假老板
That's one strike, "Mr. Fake"
但是
But
答题竞赛归我管  问题归我问
I'm running this quiz show, I'll ask the questions
只有我才能够说但是俩字
lf there's going to be any "buts," they're going to be from me
好的  第二题
Okay, question number two
蟹黄堡一个多少钱
How much does a Krabby Patty cost?
两块九毛九
$2.99
要星期三的
On Wednesday
九毛九
99 cents
又答对了
Right again
你现在越看越假了
You're starting to look pretty phony right about now
我要是你的话就特别紧张了
I'd be nervous if I were you
只有真真正正的蟹老板能答上来这题
Now, only the really real Mr. Krabs can answer this
如果在一月第三个周三讨论秘方
If we're discussing the secret formula
on the third Wednesday in January
并且吃过香草布丁之后外面没下雨
and it's not raining outside
after we gargle with vanilla pudding
要做什么
what do we do?
这道题简单
That's an easy one
就只要
You just
只要
just
我想想  如果是
Let's see, if it's a
如果是一月  吃了
If it's January with
吃了香草布丁  你会
with vanilla pudding, you
跳过吧
Pass
特餐
等等
Wait
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
再给我个机会吧
Give me another chance
永别了  冒牌蟹老板
So long, Imitation Krabs
再见
Bye-bye
我就知道真货一直都是你  蟹老板
I knew it was you all along, Mr. Krabs
给你
Here you go
谢谢你了  上当宝宝
Thank you, Sponge-Dupe
你的好运硬币可别忘了
Don't forget your lucky penny
自爆
今天肯定是你的幸运日
This must be your lucky day
自爆投币口已激活
The self-destruct coin slot has been activated
十秒后起爆
Ten seconds till detonation
投币自爆
"Coin-operated self-destruct"?
这想法可不太妙
Not one of my better ideas
救命
Help
如果说那是痞老板
If that was Plankton
救命
Help
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
好好吃
Yum, yum
伸回去  你这大饿手
Back, you hungry hand, back
救命
Help
蟹老板  对不起
Gee, Mr. Krabs, I'm sorry
我还以为你是个冒牌货
I thought you were a phony
没关系的  小子
That's okay, me lad
只要秘方还能安全就行
Long as the secret formula's safe again
不过  那分钱要从你工资里扣
However, that penny's coming out of your paycheck
真的吗
Really?